http://www.iupuc.edu/privacy

HomePrivacy NoticePrivacy NoticeIUPUC (IUPUC) Privacy PolicyApplicabilityThis privacy notice applies only to the IUPUC (https://www.iupuc.edu) and explains our practices concerning the collection, use, and disclosure of visitor information. Visitor information collected by IUPUC will be used only as outlined in this privacy notice.Other units at the university may collect and use visitor information in different ways. Therefore, visitors to other university websites should review the privacy notices for the particular sites they visit. IUPUC is not responsible for the content of other websites or for the privacy practices of websites outside the scope of this notice.ChangesBecause Internet technologies continue to evolve rapidly, IUPUC may make appropriate changes to this notice in the future. Any such changes will be consistent with our commitment to respecting visitor privacy, and will be clearly posted in a revised privacy notice.Collection and UsePassive/Automatic CollectionWhen you view pages on our site, the web server automatically collects certain technical information from your computer and about your connection.This website is hosted on Webserve, a shared web–hosting environment provided by IU’s University Information Technology Services. For more information about privacy practices related to Webserve, read the Webserve Privacy Notice Supplement.In addition to any information collected by Webserve, our server and/or site collects the following:user-specific information on which pages are visitedthe referring websitethe date and time of visitthe duration of visityour browser typeyour screen resolutionContinued use of our website indicates consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of this information as described in this notice.This technical information is not retained or utilized.Active/Manual/Voluntary CollectionWe will not attempt to collect any information from you through the use of forms or other type of manual input.Information Used For ContactIf you supply us with your postal/mailing address:You will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.Information SharingWe do not share any aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with other entities or organizations.We do not share any personally identifiable information with other entities or organizations, except when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website.Except as described above, we will not share any information with any party for any reason.Except as provided in the Disclosure of Information section below, we do not attempt to use the technical information discussed in this section to identify individual visitors.CookiesA cookie is a small data file that is written to your hard drive that contains information about your visit to a web page. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you may configure your browser not to accept them at all, or to notify and require approval before accepting new cookies. Some web pages/sites may not function properly if the cookies are turned off, or you may have to provide the same information each time you visit those pages.In order to customize the information and services offered to you, our site uses cookies to:store visitors preferencesrecord session information, such as items that visitors add to their shopping cartChildrenThis site is not directed to children under 13 years of age, does not sell products or services intended for purchase by children, and does not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and teachers to be involved in children’s Internet explorations. It is particularly important for parents to guide their children when they are asked to provide personal information online.SMS Text Message Terms of ServiceWhen you "opt-in" for one or more text messaging programs (“Service”), you expressly consent to receive non-marketing and marketing texts messages from IUPUC and others texting on its behalf, including automated technology such as autodialers, at the telephone number(s) that you provide, and agree to be bound by these SMS Terms and Conditions.In order to use the Service, you must be a resident of the United States and be 18 years of age or older.To opt-in to receive IUPUC CRM Initiative alerts, go to (https://crm.iu.edu/sms/text-subscribe-XXXXX.html). Upon your opt-in, you will receive IUPUC CRM text messages intended to provide you with information about IUPUC CRM Initiative. Message and data rates may apply.You will receive a variable number of text messages per month.IUPUC does not charge for the Service, however, message and data rates may apply to each text message sent or received in connection with this Service. Please contact your mobile telephone carrier for pricing plans.You can cancel this Service at any time. Just text "STOP" to XXXXX. We will send you a reply message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed. After this, you will no longer receive messages from usText "HELP" to XXXXX for help. We will respond with instructions on how to use our service as well as how to unsubscribe.Supported Carriers may change from time to time, but currently include the following: AT&T, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, T-Mobile, U.S. Cellular, Boost Mobile, MetroPCS, Virgin Mobile, Alaska Communications Systems (ACS), Appalachian Wireless (EKN), Bluegrass Cellular, Cellular One of East Central, IL (ECIT), Cellular One of Northeast Pennsylvania, Cricket, Coral Wireless (Mobi PCS), COX, Cross, Element Mobile (Flat Wireless), Epic Touch (Elkhart Telephone), GCI, Golden State, Hawkeye (Chat Mobility), Hawkeye (NW Missouri), Illinois Valley Cellular, Inland Cellular, iWireless (Iowa Wireless), Keystone Wireless (Immix Wireless/PC Man), Mosaic (Consolidated or CTC Telecom), Nex-Tech Wireless, NTelos, Panhandle Communications, Pioneer, Plateau (Texas RSA 3 Ltd), Revol, RINA, Simmetry (TMP Corporation), Thumb Cellular, Union Wireless, United Wireless, Viaero Wireless, and West Central (WCC or 5 Star Wireless).T-Mobile is not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.IUPUC is not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. Delivery of information and content to a mobile device may fail due to a variety of circumstances or conditions. You understand and acknowledge that network services, including but not limited to mobile network services, are outside of IU’s control, and IU is not responsible or liable for issues arising from them.Use of Third Party ServicesThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies (described above) to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including possibly your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google.For more information, please visit Google’s Privacy Policy.Disclosure of InformationWe may share some aggregate information with other appropriate university personnel and units to ensure the quality, functionality, and security of our website/application.Any other disclosure—with appropriate external parties such as law enforcement agencies—will be done in accordance with all applicable laws and university policies in order to investigate and respond to suspected violations of law or university policy.SecurityDue to the rapidly evolving nature of information technologies, no transmission of data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. While we are committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to university websites, and you do so at your own risk. However, once we receive your information, we will use reasonable safeguards consistent with prevailing industry standards and commensurate with the sensitivity of the data being stored to maintain the security of that information on our systems.In addition, we will comply with all applicable federal, state and local laws regarding the privacy and security of visitor information.Privacy Notice ChangesFrom time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.Contact InformationIf you have questions or concerns about this policy, please contact us.IUPUC4601 Central AvenueColumbus, IN 47203co-webwork@iupuc.edu812.375.7555ATTN: IUPUC Web TeamIf you feel that this site is not following its stated policy and communicating with the owner of this site does not resolve the matter, or if you have general questions or concerns about privacy or information technology policy at Indiana University, please contact the chief privacy officer through the University Information Policy Office, 812-855-UIPO, privacy@iu.edu.
Twitter
Facebook
Instagram
LinkedIn
Contact, Address and Additional Links
Services
Canvas
One.IU
Clery Act Information
The Annual Security and Fire Safety Report, containing policy statements, crime and fire statistics for all Indiana University campuses, is available online. You may also request a physical copy by emailing IU Public Safety at iups@iu.edu or by visiting IUPD.
IUPUC
4601 Central Avenue
Columbus, IN 47203
Campus: 812.348.7311
Admissions: 812.348.7390
